<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS General News</title>
    <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/</link>
    <description>Dublin Bus General News</description>
    <item>
      <title>Dublin Legend Philly McMahon’s HalfTimeTalk CLG Scores  Top Dublin Bus Community Spirit Award </title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Dublin-Legend-Philly-McMahons-HalfTimeTalk-CLG-Scores--Top-Dublin-Bus-Community-Spirit-Award-/</link>
      <description>Today, Monday November 6, Dublin footballing legend Philly McMahon visited his old school, Holy Spirit Boys National School, Ballymun, with Senator Lynn Ruane and former Ireland international soccer star Niall Quinn where he accepted a Dublin Bus Community Spirit Award for €5,000 on behalf of his charity HalfTimeTalk CLG. The award will go to helping the important work of HalfTimeTalk CLG which...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Dublin-Legend-Philly-McMahons-HalfTimeTalk-CLG-Scores--Top-Dublin-Bus-Community-Spirit-Award-/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 13:44:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revised Dublin Bus Fares from 1 December, 2017 </title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Revised-Dublin-Bus-Fares-from-1-December-2017-/</link>
      <description>Dublin Bus wishes to advise customers that following a determination by the National Transport Authority (NTA) revised fares will apply to some cash and Leap fares which will come into effect from 1 December, 2017. An additional year of free travel will be given to our younger customers as children up to 5 years of age will travel for free on Dublin Bus.&amp;nbsp; There is no change to fares for shorter...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Revised-Dublin-Bus-Fares-from-1-December-2017-/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 12:46:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversion on Routes 15a and 15b</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Diversion-on-Routes-15a-and-15b/</link>
      <description>Dublin Bus wishes to advise customers that to due to maintenance works, Samuel Beckett Bridge will be closed during the time below; Monday 13 November 2017, from 21.00 hours until 06.00 hours. Tuesday 14 November 2017, from 21.00 hours until 06.00 hours. Wednesday 15 November 2017, from 21.00 hours until 06.00 hours. As a result the below diversions will be in place. Routes 15a and 15b &amp;nbsp; All...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Diversion-on-Routes-15a-and-15b/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 11:53:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversions on Routes 7, 84 and 111</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Diversions-on-Routes-7-84-and-111/</link>
      <description>We wish to advise customers that due to roadworks, Routes 7, 84 and 111 will be unable to serve Brides Glen, Cherrywood Business Park and Wyattville Link Road from Friday 17 November 2017 at 20.00hrs to 18.00hrs Sunday 19 November 2017. As a result the following diversions will be in place; Route 7 Towards Brides Glen Normal route to Wyattville Road, divert to N11, Loughlinstown Roundabout,...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Diversions-on-Routes-7-84-and-111/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 14:53:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversions due to Christmas Light Procession</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Diversions-due-to-Christmas-Light-Procession/</link>
      <description>Dublin Bus wishes to advise customers that in order to facilitate the Christmas Lights Procession on O’Connell Street, the below diversion will be in place from 16:00hrs to 19:00hrs on Sunday 19 November 2017. Routes 1, 9, 11, 13, 16, 38/a/b/d, 40, 44, 46a, 122, 140 and City Tours.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Towards D'Olier Street Normal Route to junction with Cathal Brugha Street then divert left to Cathal Brugha...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Diversions-due-to-Christmas-Light-Procession/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 09:37:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversions due to Run in the Dark Dublin 2017</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Diversions-due-to-Run-in-the-Dark-Dublin-2017/</link>
      <description>We wish to advise customers that due to Run in the Dark Dublin on Wednesday 22 November 2017 the below road closures will be in place: Custom House Quay 19.00hrs to 21.30hrs. Matt Talbot Memorial Bridge 20.00hrs to 20.10hrs. North Wall Quay 19.30hrs to 23.00hrs. City Quay, Sir Rogerson's Quay, Macken Street 19.30hrs to 21.30hrs.&amp;nbsp; As a result the following diversions will take place; Route 1 Fro...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Diversions-due-to-Run-in-the-Dark-Dublin-2017/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 10:55:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revised Timetable on Route 747 </title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Revised-Timetable-on-Route-747-/</link>
      <description>We wish to advise customers of a revised timetable on Route 747. From Monday 6 November 2017, a Winter timetable will be in operation for Route 747. The buses will operate every 15 minutes Monday to Friday, Saturday and Sunday.&amp;nbsp; View revised Route 747 Customers can also get updates on&amp;nbsp; Facebook , follow us on Twitter&amp;nbsp; @dublinbusnews &amp;nbsp;or call our customer service line on (01) 8734222, lines open...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Revised-Timetable-on-Route-747-/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 09:55:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversions on Routes 33, 33a and 33x</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Diversions-on-route-33-33a-and-33x/</link>
      <description>We wish to advise customers that due to major drainage works, the R128 north of Rush Village is closed from Monday 11 September until Friday 10 November 2017. We will resume full service on Route 33/a/x from 13.00hrs on that day. The following diversions will be in place; Routes 33, 33a and 33x Towards Skerries Normal route to Station Road at Lusk Village, left to R127 ring road, right to...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Diversions-on-route-33-33a-and-33x/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 15:06:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporary Terminus on Routes 40d and 238</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Temporary-Terminus-on-Routes-40d-and-238/</link>
      <description>We wish to advise customers that due to road repair works Routes 40d and 238 will have a temporary terminus in Tyrrelstown from Wednesday 25 October 2017 until Monday 4 December. As a result buses will be unable to serve stops 7072&amp;nbsp; (Tyrrelstown, Carlton Hotel)&amp;nbsp;and 7073&amp;nbsp; (Tyrrelstown, Carlton Hotel) and Blanchardstown Carlton Hotel. Towards Tyrrelstown buses will terminate at stop 6005...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Temporary-Terminus-on-Routes-40d-and-238/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:59:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revised Timetable on Route 27a</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Revised-Timetable-on-Route-27a/</link>
      <description>We are pleased to announce a revised timetable on Route 27a, from Sunday 22 October 2017.&amp;nbsp; As a result of customer feedback there will be timetable changes to Monday to Friday and Sunday departures. These changes will improve service reliability and punctuality.&amp;nbsp; View Revised Route 27a All changes have been approved by the National Transport Authority. Customers can also get updates on&amp;nbsp; Faceboo...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Revised-Timetable-on-Route-27a/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 13:57:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revised Timetable on Route 53</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Revised-Timetable-on-Route-53/</link>
      <description>We are pleased to announce a revised timetable on Route 53, from Sunday October 22 2017.&amp;nbsp; As a result of customer feedback there will be timetable changes to Monday to Friday departures. These changes will improve service reliability and punctuality.&amp;nbsp; View revised Route 53 All changes have been approved by the National Transport Authority. Customers can also get updates on&amp;nbsp; Facebook , follow us...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Revised-Timetable-on-Route-53/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 14:48:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lucan Shopping Centre Roadshow</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Lucan-Shopping-Centre-Roadshow/</link>
      <description>At Dublin Bus, our 128 million customers are at the heart of everything we do. We value their feedback and use information from them to help us improve our services. As such, we are hosting a roadshow at Lucan Shopping Centre to give customers the opportunity to provide feedback and suggestions to us about our services in the Lucan area. The roadshow takes place this Friday October 20 from...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Lucan-Shopping-Centre-Roadshow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 13:20:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advice for customers on refunds due to unlawful picketing of Dublin Bus garages on 31 March</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Advice-for-customers-on-refunds-due-to-unlawful-picketing-of-Dublin-Bus-garages-on-31-March/</link>
      <description>Dublin Bus will issue customers with annual or monthly bus only tickets and bus/Luas tickets on leap cards with a refund for the hours of lost service due to the unlawful picketing of Dublin Bus garages on 31 March 2017.&amp;nbsp; We will commence refunding once the Bus Éireann dispute has concluded.&amp;nbsp; To facilitate ease of collection, we are currently developing an online application process which will...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Advice-for-customers-on-refunds-due-to-unlawful-picketing-of-Dublin-Bus-garages-on-31-March/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 15:27:16 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dublin Bus proud to sponsor Bike Locker initiative</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Dublin-Bus-proud-to-sponsor-Bike-Locker-initiative/</link>
      <description>Dublin Bus is proud to partner with South Dublin County Council as official sponsors of bikelocker.ie‘s new locker facilities beside our bus stop 2234, Lucan.&amp;nbsp; This initiative provides customers with a more attractive overall network by pairing the bus with increased cycle facilities. If you live in the Lucan area then the fastest way to get to Dublin City is by Bus. Dublin Bus Routes 25,...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Dublin-Bus-proud-to-sponsor-Bike-Locker-initiative/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 09:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legends Competition – T&amp;Cs</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Legends-Competition--TCs/</link>
      <description>Terms &amp;amp; Conditions for 30th Birthday Competition (the “Terms and Conditions”) 1. This competition is availble to all those who are 18+, resident in the Republic of Ireland and complete a valid entry via Dublin Bus News social channels: Facebook and Twitter. 2. The promoter of this competition is Bus Átha Cliath-Dublin Bus, 59 Upper O’Connell Street, Dublin 1, Ireland (Company Registration No....</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Legends-Competition--TCs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 08:53:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning 30 Club – T&amp;Cs</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Turning-30-Club--TCs/</link>
      <description>Terms &amp;amp; Conditions for Turning 30 Club (the “Terms and Conditions”) 1. This promotion is only available to those born between January 1st 1987 and December 31st 1987. 2. Those who are not born between Januay 1st 1987 and December 31st 1987 can enter the Dublin Bus competition for a chance to win other great prizes, entry on www.dublinbus30club.com . 3. The promoter of this competition is Bus Át...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/Turning-30-Club--TCs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 08:21:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30th Birthday Snapchat Competition – T&amp;Cs</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/30th-Birthday-Snapchat-Competition--TCs/</link>
      <description>Terms &amp;amp; Conditions for 30th Birthday Competition (the “Terms and Conditions”) 1. This competition is availble to all those who are resident in the Republic of Ireland and complete a valid entry via Dublin Bus on Snapchat. 2. The promoter of this competition is Bus Átha Cliath-Dublin Bus, 59 Upper O’Connell Street, Dublin 1, Ireland (Company Registration No. 119569) (“Dublin Bus”). 3. Employees...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/News-Centre/General-News/30th-Birthday-Snapchat-Competition--TCs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 17:17:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dublin Bus and Social Media</title>
      <link>http://www.dublinbus.ie/About-Us/Dublin-Bus-and-Social-Media-/</link>
      <description>Dublin Bus are now Tweeting. Dublin Bus Twitter Content Policy: We want people to feel comfortable and happy to be in our social space. We want @DublinBusNews to be a forum for everyone. The tweets should be respectful and contain language that is appropriate for all groups and ages. If necessary we reserve the right to block and report tweets that are obscene, indecent; contain threats or...</description>
      <guid>http://www.dublinbus.ie/About-Us/Dublin-Bus-and-Social-Media-/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 09:50:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
